trafficzap.com 2017-12-16

# TrafficZap Free Traffic

Island Media, the operator of this website, is committed to practices and technologies that respect the privacy of our visitors. This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices for this website and all other websites in the Island Media Network.

Island Media does not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as your name, phone number, or e-mail address. This information is only obtained if you provide it voluntarily, through contacting us via e-mail, or through an online form. Any personal information you do provide is managed only to the extent that any desired or necessary communication with you may be undertaken.

**Information collected automatically via the Internet**  
Island Media logs all requests to our servers. These logs capture computer information, navigation and clickstream data. Some of the information collected does not identify who you are. Other information, such as your domain name or IP address, may identify you depending on the naming standards followed by your Internet service provider. While we make no attempt to link the information captured to the identity of individuals, the information captured does identify the following:

1\. The Internet domain and IP address from which you access our web site;  
2\. The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;  
3\. Screen resolution of your monitor;  
4\. The date and time you access our site;  
5\. The pages you visit; and  
6\. If you linked to an Island Media web site from another web site, the address of that web site.

This information is used to help us make our site more useful to our audiences by learning about the number of visitors to our site, and by monitoring traffic patterns and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about specific individuals and their visits. Visitor information is not disclosed to anyone outside the company.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of text information that is sent to your browser when you access a web site. Your browser will return this cookie information to the domain where the cookie originated. While we do not regularly use cookies to track how our visitors use the site, when cookies are used, they are usually used to help you fill in forms or track your use to help navigate your visit more efficiently.

**Cookies Used on This Site**  
This site uses cookies to track order information for paid services and/or to limit certain advertising from reaching end users. These cookies are automatically removed no longer than 24 hours after being placed.

**Security**  
For site security purposes, Island Media has installed software programs to monitor network traffic and identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage or disruption. Except in the case of authorized law enforcement investigations, no attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits.

**Privacy and Links to Other Sites**  
Island Media web sites may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other web sites and encourage you to examine each site's privacy policy and disclaimers and make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability, and correctness of material and information found.

**Information Collected in E-mails and Web Forms**  
If you should choose to provide us with personal information, such as by sending an e-mail or by filling out an online form and submitting it to us through our web site, we will use that information solely to respond to your message and to help us get the information you have requested. Island Media does not collect personal information for commercial marketing or distribution to any private organizations.

**Free Search Engine Submission Service**  
Our free search engine submission service requires us to send a valid email address to each engine listed. This address we receive is forwarded through the submission form. We do not store email addresses from this service.

**Newsletter Subscriptions**  
From time to time we send out newsletters only to subscribed users who have requested this information and who may unsubscribe at any time.
